# **Carlos Torres**

# **INSIDE SALES - Telecommications**

Roseville, CA torcarl22@aol.com - 916.217.1082

Business to Business specialist. Well versed with SMB. Love to work hard and achieve results. Focused on working, not a a cell phone. I understand what it takes to succeed and will commit to success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **INSIDE SALES**

CONSOLIDATED COMMUNICATIONS - Roseville, CA -

July 2017 to Present

FAST PACE SALES AND DATA ENTRY. Data(HIGH SPEED INTERNET, Phone, and Video Sales Specialist. HIT 100% QUOTA FIRST YEAR OF EMPLOYMENT.

# **INSIDE SALES REPRESENTATIVE**

Liberty Home Equity Solutions - Rancho Cordova, CA -

January 2016 to May 2017

CLOSED 78% OF THE COLD LEADS COMPANY PROVIDED.

## **ACCOUNT MANAGER**

SureWest Communications - Roseville, CA -

September 2013 to July 2014

Business to Businees SMB.

Top performer 9 out of 11 months employed at SureWest Directories

- \* Proven new business originator finished #1 Salesperson Roseville campaign.
- \* Left due to illness

# **ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE**

VALLEY YELLOW - Sacramento, CA -

October 2009 to September 2013

- \* Top performer/Award winner; Most Accounts Sold & Dy Most New Accounts Sold
- \* Farmer: retained and increased 90% of assigned accounts;
- \* Hunter: met and exceeded new business goals in all assigned campaigns
- \* Handled over 300 accounts annually

#### **ADMISSIONS REP**

Western Career College Sacramento Ca - Sacramento, CA -

July 2007 to June 2008

Screened, sourced and selected candidates based on their qualifications, phone screens, behavioral interviews, reference checks, skills testing, drug tests and background checks

## **BANKING MORTGAGE CONSULTANT**

Washington Mutual Bank Sacramento Ca - Sacramento, CA -

April 2005 to July 2006

Self-Managed Branch home loan division \* Funded \$2 million on average month

#### LOAN ORIGINATOR

Aegis Lending Corporation - Sacramento, CA -

February 2004 to March 2005

Top producer and bonus earner at Aegis Lending Corporation, Consistently funded over \$1.5 million per month

\* Retained #1 salesman position for 6 months in a office of over 50 salesmen

**EDUCATION** 

# **Bachelor of Science in Applied Psychology**

OREGON INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

2003

**SKILLS** 

BILINGUAL (10+ years)

**CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES** 

# MLS

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Highly motivated and focused on success for all. Family person who understands importance of life. Quick learner with the ability to learn new systems rapidly.